Poor poor poor
poor
poor poor
with
our
world who are
poor have
ur poor
poor rural poor
poor rural
or or
what
advice on its first aspiration easing
samurai guy around here but there's
a big run a mile up to water now to get
a part on our Sunday morning honey like
this guy gets paid to go fishing while we
slave over
a hot car but he's going to identity that
room for one more logical mom when I get
back late Monday night Monday night the
lets me and I could get Monday off. So it
could get away I want to be just
I want to miss Panasonic with
a girlfriend Arabs and I busted up
a couple months ago by the way to call
you again and. She did I tell you what I
meant for the ninety time good good how do
you like this guy other than my trade my
right arm for niggers of
the run I'll be found
a new day and I spent four years in the
Navy fighting for freedom like an anchor
down the side who is going to Syria. Outer
and louder I think it is too nice to
string on she won't take no for an answer
some Dems are sure hard to shake off I
want to know
a blind boy in our name was Margie
and you know we've heard this story
a dozen times
a couple of thousand times. We begin back
all men right here that's where you'll.
Pay.
For. The
later fellows for work.
You know here. To cry about about
the. Time you get off today.
Sixty seven. Don't forget to
change. I happen to have my
autograph book here with me name
an address. Afraid you've made
a mistake I don't come with the merchants
much like. I think you're wonderful
anything wrong in the world but well enough
about you and me that. I work tonight
to let. Thirty you know like.
I think the great. Music I thought of
the campaign thirty years. Ago to give
Melissa.
A check. I just remembered.
Remember the water
was five days until payday and
flat bust how you hold. Me to.
We're going to figure out some way to get
some good this or how else am I going to
take that gorgeous creature
out to the music. That
he wouldn't give me the sweat off his
glasses. He sure did he doesn't I'm glad
you said that buzz marginals me twenty
bucks. My friend you have just read my mind
.
Oh it was large in our
place. I boy this is
a. Lesson. To let me have
a twenty bucks. That's
well believe me you're
a life saver. Without it I
can pick it up. Tomorrow
always
a boy. I need to right away. I get paid
a lot more. I understand you're.
OK thanks anyway I guess. But. I
will have them live on the washroom
May I was one of your fellows you're all
alike you don't care what you do with my
money you think I own stock
in the power company.
Said to me I was six of the five so
I said One moment. And then I said.
The supervisor the. President called
in are you listening to me. I don't
think you heard one word you
just seem to be walking around
a dream lately. Really I think of
the body of the things I have to.
Think where. Just something over
on tape. I know where you're going
and you're making
a big mistake they want to see you you
know your telephone number. But nothing
you're making
a fool of yourself. By. Well
what you need of the press sometimes you
have got time line on. A stand and I don't
. Know not you it. Sure well
if you haven't got it you
can't let the. Actual live by when it
was called him or a
person to make a call not
a matter of dollars for an action. Nobody
checks my cash except this once
a week bookkeeper and you don't come around
on Thursday I can put it back before
Thursday I can put it back tomorrow so
as I get that twenty bucks from budge.
How I left. This is
a surprise. House every little
thing just fine that's good. I'll
see later. If you've been doing
lately I want us out and. Be able to
hike you. Want to.
Remember the Sunday we had
a minor can. Do we have. A lot.
We give me a ring sometimes
Sure I'll give you
a regular get together. I'll see
later I'll. Give you rings.
Actually later. Raise your meter.
Figure out the fare as we go along.
The mind of
a charge me I might at the top
and have. But you like to
go. Let's go downtown little
shop how dull Can you get.
What I want to do with. The can
I can do something else later
you have
a deal honey. A
lot. Still here nice looking
coat but it's OK at least
a thousand bucks for
a coat like that or you can buy that mink
a bargain to two thousand. The most beautiful
thing you've ever seen in your life
it's not that I think it on time
and I want that coat. And I'm
going to get it for two thousand dollars
or whatever it takes showing it wait
a minute you really do want
to touch the bed I do.
WEDEMAN plus other blue. Brown
vs blues in your Big Brown
A Oh he was being too early
for you honey. So he goes.
Closed Monday well like that Are you sure
you didn't happen to know it was close
when you invited me so I know what I do
a thing like that particular place you want
to go name it you can have. All right.
All right. I know
a place where I'd like to go. Out
and lunch and you're hearing say all
of the government going on you. Met
a. God you want to break them
a. Voice you. Hear an echo
then I'll show you how to
beat this game.
The. One evil they make claiming I hit
the jackpot.
Job for you now wait
a minute. Go ahead on it
play as much as you will
that David and I can handle
next. I used to work.
At nine and. Come back. Still in the
window naked so I guess it is
crazy what do you think I am
a millionaire. What's going on here.
Let's get this and I will have
a picture painted on. The latent. Who goes
first we both go.
Where you want me I have a box with
a nickel. Here. Now
what do you want Johnny nine Echo's
a buddy. Who is cheating well. Look
you've got your nickel Haven't you
had to rub.
My fellow man look I've got the rules in
this house that goes for you too you want
to pull that kind of stuff for
somewhere else. Some of the.
Time here let's get out
of this crummy job.
Combine it with
a the sale and the ha ha
ha ha ha.
Depicts darling. The speakers here. Who
Use years even to save us
because they. Lose the.
US that I used to know with the names of
all the sun you know I never saw stunted I
was sixteen. Rock up. I was
raised in steel town with the kid you
couldn't see the sky the snow so I ran away
Funny I ran away Paul. But it was
a lot of times. What you
do if you run away.
I was caught for a while waiting
to be a joint. Clerk in
a five and ten in the coffee shop. Is now
what you run away to which run away from
I run away from
a farm about the old man used with all men
which are free with us so far and away
from
a lot of things. Get drunk all the time
and never have any east coast where. And
the boarders especially those boys they
wouldn't leave me alone musta been.
A learn to handle
a master while. I think
you could handle me. I
can handle you.
I was was there it was. Their
profession party I want
to be back. On our Never
mind. I'll call him later
by.
The people what's he doing here two days
ahead of time if you find out I'm sure
he'll tell you oh man you know
man's mean enough to send
a got to jail just for laughs
I gotta get twenty bucks in
a hurry. How about that
shall we loan out to
the one that's always yet been on the
radio lookin with an honest face walk out
with
a pocket full of dope. I musta walked
in with the wrong Thanks couple
days to check my references I haven't
got any references and I have got
a couple of days.
And I have a for a dollar down like
a Cessna one as soon as we check up
on your credit. I can't wait that
long to wait
a minute you've got to try
to. Know Yes yes I have at
the hub at the hub where I buy my clothes
I tell you what I'll do I'll call the
credit manager and if he says you're OK
you can take the watch right which is OK
let's get it on Chile
and what it looks like.
How much could you let me have on this.
Let me find.
Any better than last week I don't know yet
Mr legend about that other matter see if
you can find a way to make it
a business deduction I think about. Early
this week I. Had some tax reports.
And I think it is I was here
I got my Thursday work done.
I just checked the register and it's
twenty dollars short. Maybe could've made
a mistake and. Checked it. You
know sometimes the money gets
stuck in the money.
But I looked in the money.
Just didn't look good.
Ready.
I'm Moriarty Eliphalet investigations are.
To watch yesterday Jays jewelers and.
Straight on Bill Johnson hock to. My
desk played dumb why would you buy
a watch for one hundred dollars pocket the
same day for thirty. Because you don't
and that's why. I signed up ten bucks
a month. Ten bucks. Because Jay jewelers
don't think you're going to be here when
the month they think you're going to
skip town so you'll pay up now R.J.
Going to swear I want. For what
I'll give it to you in words of one
syllable my friend when you buy something
on the installment plan your time what
they call
a conditional sales contract. This contract
says that the watch the radio or the
easy chair don't belong to you until you
make your last payment it says if you sell
mortgage or hock something you
don't know. You're guilty. And
a hundred dollar watch is grand larceny.
That's three years in the penitentiary and
this. Kid. May.
Find
a contract like this the. Debt
is paid within twenty four hours
or charges will be brought.
I can't get a hold of
a hundred bucks I mean just like that right
away you better dig it up somewhere.
Because if you're. Going
to call on you with
a big. Brother
.
I do and. Usually have my watch.
A great.
Maybe I can get some thought my Chalabi
I wonder how much they'll give me for.
No dice what good is three hundred bucks
I still owe the finance company three
fifty.
I have passed
a dog tried everything I could think of
and I still haven't raised one hundred
dollars I had raised a buck and
a quarter so I threw in the towel and
headed for Phil's place to knock off
a couple of beers.
Longer I sat on that silly story the
more I felt like slugging somebody like
a sock doorman makan for being so tight on
the guy in the jewelry store for sending
Moriarty after me or the fella standing
next to me at the bar because he had money
in his pocket and I did. I'm going
to. Research for sure right.
OK I've got to get home before you chaps
my. Ever got some smaller This was
a little high listen. It's
another fifty let me.
Buy right there on time. Which
is get this shit I gotta
get home before they always
do and actually know.
Why oh. Yeah they only
build a long story as
a joke or like that radio let the draw do
you wrong the bingo game to the suckers
keep him happy. Another
beer Downing. Shots of.
All right now it's like.
I don't want your maybe you don't
want to lead nowhere yes. I have my
choice. The. Same is.
The. Same or is.
Your world worth. My.
Words are.
We can reach some of us can you go. Like
one in the back to settle for free.
I am glad. I was I know that. I believe.
I think that it's wonderful to see yourself
but wait for. It and I have to tell you
that after anybody for
a million things. Was
a rush but he's chasing us. Right
now. About to change this we've got
to light up places where maybe you've got
all night me and Helen we only got five
minutes or a show. Of just under
a million I got I've already seen this
year I saw him down have just said.
I got it with mine if I was you
know I would think him either
by. Season and this is like oh.
That's going to go across Europe
and the shoes and the
diplomats go on every. Ride.
My knees really shaken back to I thought
the cops and bust out of that alley any
minute havoc Naaman the clear the heavy
door in my pocket I can pay off the jewelry
store and have enough left over the
shoulder of the biggest time she ever had.
There I got
a big weather tonight I promise
to meet her in next place. What
time is. Twenty five ten. Only smoke I
promise you the guy have power gone
right away to get denied and I walk into
the bus I'm with you don't have to say I
can get home I. Will give you
a ring and we will get together
sometime soon I'll see you later.
Don't come back I want my
fifty dollars to do me
a favor way yes. Drop. It just.
Take your hands out I
was. Like the push to.
Try. This is.
How it's always about fifty
dollars It wasn't alone it was
a present. I don't you're
taking fifty dollars from
a guy like yourself. Get outta here.
Her whole.
Body. When you going to tell me what
resulted was we celebrated some
to me last night you were spending dollar
bill good night and. I was one of the
crappy. Sure wasn't even
go to champagne corks.
But I mean they. Just thought
you might want to show them
a cape. Given that idea. Maybe it was
Evelyn. Evelyn who suffered.
Bookkeeper in the movie house.
He saw
a surety lose in Europe.
What do you know but. She
just came in the next place to phone
the cops cops but she say they're
a long time no see how about
a dead no thank you boyfriend Well my
bank. Would break into anything I can do
boy yeah blow you heard her.
Say. The chill the guy who did it with
a handkerchief around it. He
took Shorty first. Bankroll.
Didn't. Follow I know.
Just like you might have
heard about. Any outfit with me and
I want any fifty dollar bills.
I wouldn't go spending them around the pier
Yeah why not. With everyone around who
knows it sure to carry fifty.
On a guy named Shorty and I want this done
a crap game say hello now
sure you do. That stems and.
That's that's why I can. Only. SPEND.
SPEND.
Forty sixty others decided out you
don't. Know if you're gonna drive.
Well already.
Back
a motor boat. This is I'm speaking. What
I like to what. I'd like to take
a big jump off the pier you
know I don't like to take
a jump off the pier but you better come
and see me or else Or else what around
something is going to happen
to you. To you Dan in point.
What.
What's on your mind in
a better be good or it's very good you
know last night surprise part of the big
prize fight you left home in your I picked
it up picked it up where you left it got
a nap in it you know like like us for
a mess because I'm in. A row and you're
talking about snow but I'll take it just
for luck Sure sure you do you keep my
handkerchief I I keep your handkerchief same
not only on the your handkerchief
good blood on it so what did you have
a year anybody's say money talks. Fifty
dollar bills paid top very loud big
bills what do they say. To Shorty McCabe
who is in the cave and that's what it says
Shorty McCain what you're doing and what
you're trying to tell me I'm telling you
about the hold up see everything
from the pictures show she she shot
a man get drubbed and she got
a very good look at the guy who did
it she sings you can identify him
a very easy nice girl you want me to call
him and I did that. You're so sure that I
was mixed up in this thing why don't
you call the cops caps on. I'm
a business man she Danny Boy I think I can
do business with you very nice What kind
of business do you think you could do
with me automobile business you get me
a new car and and I don't know
nothing just nothing. No car.
I could get a new car if I
wanted to know who you can get
a new car seeing where you got the
fifty dollar bill. Thing in that.
I don't think so. DAVID It.
Is a place for
a reason that he was ready for delivery
in the morning at all and very best of
that we catch up with the ten gallons
of gas this time six is plenty.
There goes the last new car we'll have
this month I've got to get tonight or blow
town tomorrow even if I blow town they'll
probably catch up with me. Boy am I in
a mess. Today than I am I
was just thinking if I
can take Helen out anymore I thought maybe
I'd recall some time. Sure when she
didn't or.
When.
One.
Of us. This thing is stuck back.
In your dreams today in
a second California Street got life just.
Fine. I promise you I know nothing
trips of which I don't think of.
This and I'm
a little in the moment the kid.
Going into the car. Business and. I
tell you I'm actually to again with
a friend of mine driving it home to Nevada
that he doesn't want to run because.
He's going to.
Right. Now I know who took
their dreams and then.
Do. I could tell the police about it right
this minute but I don't know why that
would help me get back the
car and I understand. I
don't I'm not interested in sending anybody
to jail I'm interested in getting back
that car. I don't know why you're
telling me all this and all you
should do and apply this firm's go at Sedan
and I happen to know it is because it
was think. You're trying to get this thing
on maybe not about to try to run any
bluffs on my time so I had to tell you not
to tell me anything all you have to do
is to get that car down there parked up
front before I get down tomorrow. If I
haven't got it what if I don't know what
you're doing already why don't you Mark.
That return the car I had to pay
for it three thousand dollars. For
a thousand dollars. And only left for
a night event do you not think so that you
would list the thousand dollars what I
like may get it I don't like that
everybody's got a family some folks got
a lot it's probably keep
a man out of jail. I'll give you
twenty four hours Friday I want
some money or I want. A Let me give you
some warning don't you probably found.
Three thousand dollars it might as well
been three million I try to remember who
got to see me in the green sedan nobody
knowing I had it except. Nick maybe that
was who told the old man make
a good. Friend. What's
the matter with you tonight
you look like a lost
a last friend. To go to Texas
honey right now right.
What's the matter with California.
Where the getting to wrong.
Tell your boss the. Worst jam
when ever my boss is going
to throw me in the brig if I don't get
a hold of three thousand bucks or else we're
going to get all three thousand bucks
. I know it is three or
four thousand dollars.
First national but no not many bank we can
get out of with get out of these. All
you have to do is to break
a little catch lock on
a rickety old door. Try to your thing in
there with my fingers. I'm in too deep
already.
This is the end of the month. That's when
it keeps the money overnight. I mean look
at the Penny Arcade. They'll be
thousands of dollars it and I. Would
not be the one that's going to. Try to
people for cash and take. A big payday lot
of them and bring their checks in in the
morning before the banks open. And he
doesn't even have
a safe he hides it. I know where. Liquor
got me and. Nick get you out.
When you have to go to to. Stay
here. With.
Someone watching us from.
Going the old New Coke the landlady she's
always looking for trouble you know I had
a news program on the air the other night
and she but didn't try to tell me that
a man in my room. We still watch.
Let's give us something to watch.
They out here in the got to
watch. But the incoming L.
Consequent lot three types all
know it feels. Good luck.
Why.
Get out of your choice.
Get the money and you're choosing what
happened I watch McSorley. These are the big
chance tonight you got
away with here to be take
a look at this I'm not. I feel
like I'm being shoved into
a corner I don't get out so they'll be too
late maybe it's too late already we can
stop where. You're at right now you get
the money in your pocket to pay your way
out here trying to get the money the
square with. One how much there is
just like
a lot. Let's take it up
to my room pouted. Put
down the shades.
That's. Five hundred
eighty thank you two three
four five six seven three
five hundred dollars.
Twenty forty sixty eighty nine
eight hundred. Hundred ten.
Thirty six hundred ten dollars That's
a lot of dough money that I can make
a year working every day. It's
a copper. Just like I thought
was the big idea who
said you can come in I have rules in their
thousands of that claim respectable
place when you've got no right in here
now get out I don't allow no man in the
rooms not in my house and
I'm not leaving until he go
you are leaving right now
maybe you'd rather I'd call
a cop why you are all bad oh well you know
we don't want any trouble especially not
yet maybe I ought to go. You think you
can take care of everything right oh
yes shouldn't I don't worry I can take
care of everything I'll call you in the
morning. I don't want any of you
know look I'm the round here when you
rent the movie out sky hammocks.
Is very no back there hey you know where
nothing out today this is or what it was
you know about if you get another
day waste would you do me
a favor and shut up please R.T.
Others are day off she wouldn't get the
rest. But when she comes in would you tell
her to call Dan Brady at MAC
a motor it's very important
so she gives him. BRADY
Well I didn't see that green sedan like
this morning no you didn't you mean you
can't get it back to mean anything you
want to me and I assume you intend to pay
for the car instead how do you know I would
take it to get the money. I got it are
. Fine when you come in the office when I
haven't got around. To pick it up tonight
after work ringing in the morning why
wait for them I'll come right back at the
dentist and you can see me you know this
thing. Might be might be ten o'clock or so
. Perfectly all right see you tonight.
I came over. There where have you
been. To take care of everything all
right. That's well baby look I'll. Be over
and see you tonight since I get
off work right after six o'clock.
Yeah right.
Beautiful day. Only demean I might
never have had if it hadn't been for
you forget the cult had both but it
was what with my share the money.
He's your. Eighteen hundred
dollars you took out a don't buy
a coke with it not just a code Danny a
Maine coast has sold me out oh now just
a minute who told you where the money was
you don't know how to get it isn't that
worth half I can use have
any three thousand Don't be
a chump nobody expects to get everything
asked for make him an offer that's what I
did want you dead sure this could
quit two thousand that I told
a story eight hundred all I had
a good take it and leave it took it. Up
to the old man done it so he could rig
I bet anything it takes.
Right here I'm glad you're
doing the sensible thing.
But only eighteen under you that's right
where is the rest of it you couldn't dig
it up I got to leave it. OK it's.
Just. That.
Up in the police station that's the idea
I told you I'd forget about the whole
thing for three thousand dollars but not
for eighteen hundred hours you've got the
rest of it on you you'd better pay me now
before it's too late why good for without
my help our way of life.
That's.
Why.
When. One.
When
.
One
when
.
I missed the quitting time
and I want to say goodbye. I
told you what I try to. Do remember. Well
the next morning he called me that up
then tried to tell me. About somebody
drive away. He said that he saw
you drive that car with. Me as
often happens.
Around put the pressure on everybody hopes
that would turn. Some of these days I
was going to get
a. Second. Coming
out and trying to outsmart
everybody but he got too smart.
He was the bomb.
We got to get out what are you talking about
trying to call the cops I had to stop
. Things. And try
to call the cops to take the phone
away from. The level on the level.
Of the morning by that time will be half
way to. You'll be halfway to Texas not me
but the consul be after us they will be
after me I don't have to run away or in
this thing together you told me off from
adults I didn't tell you to kill em and I
wasn't there when it happened so why should
I stick my neck out more that kind of
a dame Are you the kind of watch out for
yourself I didn't who would. For you don't
care about anybody else to you why sure
I'd do I had I wouldn't want to see
anything happen to you Danny certainly
wouldn't want to see the cops catch you and
then you better get started to take. Our
love. To see goodbye if you want me to
but I would only my left.
One mark like.
Ms Nowak said just to see.
What I am got for you yet.
Whether there are such ones.
What you got in the first lady.
But. You won't find him in there
won't find it all in there you know damn
BRADY Oh then read it when I find it
getting out of the status fast as you can
drive why aren't you getting up to I
didn't have any part of it I didn't even
know no I'm. Are you trying to make me
look like
a fool Mackey of course which Mikey is that
the one that ran the automobile agency
ran when he can keep on running it now
that he's dead Kenny. Who's dead Mackie of
course Brady killed him the girl didn't
have any part of it where did it happen you
know where at the autumn. Say
are you trying to kid me
sure maybe it's the other way around maybe
you're trying to kid me why did you
start spilling the minute I came in the
door maybe it's because you wanted me to
think your boyfriend
is gone when he had. I
know I know if I'm still here. Right into
the GOING TO THE COUCH I don't suppose
he'd be that near. And I didn't
think you'd be that close.
But it. Watches. Ha
ha. Ha ha where is
a dame like you'll get
a cold like this I bought that car with my
own money you take your dirty hands off
it. I can prove it I I got
a receipt. Alaska for
years nine seventeen Main Street received
a very Novak eighteen hundred dollars. Well
it looks like the right hunch Nic what
do you suppose brought us here last night
somebody stole thirty six hundred dollars
of next money of the day you
paid eight hundred dollars for
a fur coat looks like you and your boyfriend
split makes bank roll right down the
middle I don't know what you're talking
about give me back my toe not really we'll
take it right whether right or
a lot of money we'll check on might be
on the way to either station. Section.
When.
What do you do here I can see you were
trouble so I got to talk to right back home
I got to get out of what it. Was the whole
of the office but you know about that.
When I was
a million I was I couldn't see your
features but I knew that it was you then I
thought. You know how it is when you love
someone you think you see him fifty times
a day I'm going to let you call my name
and I turned around and there you were.
About to hold up the on
a park I saw the look that all. I wanted
to get out let me get started. I thought
oh please come on the house with her I have
to use one of the our orders of yours I
can help you I can tell them you want me
Ali You know I have an alibi I don't get
what you want to help me think about
my way all I ever gave you was
a run around in
a camel Why don't you get smart stay away
from me I've been away too long I didn't
any good I did I got oh I'm dumb to throw
myself I got out of the gym I got no I'm
always that I was going to run out of waiting
for you to come out of nowhere I know
. I fell in love with. First time
I saw you. I'll drive you home.
Less than
a week since Helen waited for me outside
the garage if you've been dancing like me
she said no I had to do was say swell idea
let's go out tonight but I said that I
wouldn't be running away
from the cops tonight
a murder hanging over my head. No
no. Anybody further to the curb.
Let's take
a look at your driver's
license. Right. That's
your name sure. It was through
Boulevard stuff back there.
When you sign this. Yes.
I. Think it is.
Telling you kept me from making an awful
mistake if you only take me with you I
could help you I know I say let me lay it
all. I'm going to have to keep running
I'm going to keep running all my life
because when they catch up with me they're
going to hang me. For murder. I killed
a man right. Stuck up then tell me how to.
Telling her about it was as hard as I thought
it to be and it was Helen who came up
with the idea of Mexico we decided to head
for an inland town like our Maceo were
not many tourists come a man could
be saved but the three years in
a place like that. That's
goodbye to Mexico.
It's the main bearings
will take a couple of days
a fix for they will have to hitchhike to
get there by morning we'd never make it we
have to. Or Helen I've had the right girl
all the time we too dumb to know about it
if we ever get out of this place we're
going to happen how. I've got an idea that
this is the baby that's going to get us
there we're going to the south get us
a lift on English straight through
to Mexico and I'm careful.
Getting quick I'll try the funny stuff I
don't want to hurt you all right when the
signal changes get going turns out and I
would get under fifty and over twenty
would like understanding.
Where we're going to keep
driving you'll find. I
suppose you don't know what
you're getting into this isn't
a car theft it's kidnapping I want to ask
you I don't want your advice. Well I
happen to be a lawyer maybe
a good emotion to feel damaging talking
might be of help she's right whatever it is
you're running away from
Mrs Wood. Kidnapping is
a capital offense they're going to
hang you for. What's the difference.
You can hang me anywhere.
You just killed me.
How about the girl you leave her out of
a chant of the do what you understand me.
I believe that's what we're the police.
Looks on I can see this girl means something
to you. Why don't you tell me what
happened for her sake she need
a lawyer sooner or later.
Maybe you're right.
If you're sure you could keep her in the
clear if she's innocent you tell me the
whole story and it's the truth. Truth.
I don't know where to begin start
at the beginning. The guy was
a lawyer maybe you could help tell him so
I told him the whole story and I told him
about sticking up short in the out of talking
about breaking into the Penny Arcade
the most of the night I told him about here
and make an old man back and I told him
everything that happened in the
very beginning to the end. You see.
Now the first thing you want to know is
where the girl stands That's right. She's
in the clear I can't touch it but have
a day he said maybe it would be murder
it might be manslaughter Oh it's murder
alright. I might be able to get him
off with second degree and have
a hard time proving premeditation to second
degree that that I mean life with it
could. Render the whole. As
one discrepancy in your story
is what checking up on because if we get
the right answer murders out manslaughter
too Will what do you mean how do
you know he's dead. He's dead
something had fell over on the desk like
he was dead it would do that if you were
unconscious did you feel his
pulse listen. HARVEY No I didn't
men don't really. Take
a lot of killing. I can imagine Mikey
sitting in the police station right now
telling the desk man what a narrow escape.
Only was a lie Helen of the only was
a lie when I give myself up to the first
cop the came along is an all night
restaurant Why don't I use the phone find
out how Mickey is what if you keep on
driving too I'll tell you how baccy is
he's dead that's why he's dead but then
maybe it is no yes I know you listen you I
didn't want to kill anybody I don't want
to kill you now but if you try to work funny
stuff on. The blog All right so here.
But there's a some it's Saturday. So
it's in the Sunday morning. Still as
a couple hours before daylight. We
can still make it. Turn this car.
We're going now everybody's
Larson is taking
a push on without passing the exhaust
warning if we get to the pier in time I can
go when the next to come way past the
Mexican border step on at least.
The boat is still here. So there
is down there we made it.
With her I'd better hurry not you I'm going
with what I got the harbor below San
Diego at this woman from the city I'm
going with taken too many chances already
have got to go up myself on a simple reasons
I get a job you know that such a B.B.Q.
Yes but again don't go I'm so has
nothing to be afraid of. I wait
a minute maybe there is how we're going
to get this guy from going. The cops are
laughing about those out of the harbor. I
mean. I wouldn't do that if I were you by
not children the girl was in the clear she
won't be takes that gun after that she
be an accessory to know how to get well
he's right you've got to be kept out of
town somewhat now would you take
my word for something I might as
a citizen I have to notify
the police but as well as
a friend I don't have to hurry.
Would you do me another favor I can tell
about pulls out of the harbor late now I
get out of here right away.
And you haven't seen ready since noon
Monday No I haven't and you haven't heard
from either. Quit haven't
I just remembered
a funny Monday afternoon for any particular
reason. I only twenty five say they
need it as
a news broadcast to six o'clock I want to
hear talk to your heart or guarding every
airport every bus depot and
every railroad station in
a determined effort to prevent the killers
escape the four o'clock this morning
a position through roadblocks across both
state highways that are now stopping all
outbound cars but at last
reports McDonald was still
a long gun while police officers Truxton
and Chandler are dead the deputy sheriff
out on P Janice was taken to the emergency
hospital with two bullets and I'll get
it
a little closer to home beat City authorities
are seeking garage mechanic Daniel Brady
twenty six an employee of the making Motor
Company late yesterday evening watchman
Michael J.
O'BRIEN Well making his regular nightly
rounds discover the unconscious body of.
President. The automobile agency lying in
his office Mikey regained consciousness
and Mark hospital shortly after midnight
and they Brady as if they would write that
is
a lie. On your watch yourself run
and that's. What's good about it
I got my gun.
Pride. Back as I got my it was
a splinter. That my dad bore
a look at. What
. Was.
The and.
What is up and killing. Leprosy I stopped.
You think.
Of
a. Vampire
and oh it is going to. Suck What's that.
Gap the idea that. A lot
of harm what happened was
because I'm not my kind of a radio read
about what love was like I mean you're
a catalyst all. The time I don't know it's
not the money yet I am writing it's like
I was about played at the back of
General MacArthur You can write.
One of the legislature out of the locks
on the printer are left vinyl put in the
car not drive just regular hospital that's
all I would have said that much time and
what we have with. I would have gotten
me on the traffic on what you do with
a drop of. What you think they're going
to give me Have you ever been trouble for
No No Well I think we can rule out the
watch in the try to build they probably
charge you with the hold up stealing the
car and breaking into the Penny Arcade
that could add up to anything from
one to ten years but since you're
a first offender My guess
is that to be near
a one in ten whatever it is I'll take it.
Whenever he's probably waiting for it.
He went to the great gal
held. A lucky. Because both.
Lol. LOL LOL.
Lol.
LOL L.O.L.
. All right.
All right.